Alice, is this your family photo?
Yes, it is, Bob. Are these your parents?
Yes, they are. Who is he? He is my uncle, John.
Good morning, David.Good morning, Mary.
What are those in the yard?
They're ducks. They're white ducks.
Are they your ducks? No, they aren't. They're Jack's ducks.
He is my uncle. He has some geese, too.
Where are the geese? Oh, they are on the lake.
My name is Lin Hai. I am a 12-year-old middle school student.
Grace is my new friend. She is 13. She is an American girl.
Here is a photo of her family. This is her father Mr. Green. He is a PE teacher.
He likes playing tennis with Grace after school.
The woman in purple is Mrs. Green. She is an English teacher.
She has three classes in the morning and one class in the afternoon every day.
So she is busy. The little boy is Grace's brother Bob.
He likes math very much. He plays basketball every day. He thinks it's interesting.